

Amir Mehdikhani

Web Developer

Contact Information

(+60) 172244600 amir.mehdikhani@gmail.com

Live Resume

www.amir.isellx.com

Skills

Asp.net C#	
	80%
Asp.net MVC	
	90%
HTML, CSS	
	95%
Java Script	
	60%
jQuery	
	50%
SQL Server	
	70%
MySql	
	55%
Node.js	
	60%
React (js/native)	
	75%

Summary

I'm a creative Front-End developer with more than 10 years of experience in designing and developing UI/UX, testing, debuging and training staff within eCommerce technologies. I'm very passionate, hard worker, enthusiastic, motivated I always looking for a job which I can show my talents and knowledge to improve my experience as well.

Education

Associate degree of Software Computer Engineer (IT) University of Applied Science (IRAN) Graduate of 2011

Diploma Of Electronic Navid school Graduate of 2008

Work History

Full stack developer

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020

Arra Gemilang Sdn. Bhd.

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- . Manage team of developers to develop ecommerce installment platform for Venddor CO-OP.
- . Report and update database for all users (salary, instalment,) and sales in live chart.
- . Give access to all vendors see them sales and profit in them control panel

Senior Developer

May 2018 - May 2019

AE Production Adn. Bhd.

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- . Develope photography studio website with ASP.NET MVC4 tech.
- . Program membership system with strap card system to have more discunt and more benefits.

Web designer and Developer

Jun 2016 - Mar 2018

Tamay Business Group

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- . Develope E-commerce website with ASP.NET MVC4 technology.
- . design and develop full database system with sql server to save all users data to runing member ship system.
- . Program membership system with strap card for deposite and get free products as intrest of invest.